const dayTwentySixQuestions = [
  {
    question:
      "Which ‘Surah’ of the Quran ends with names of two Prophets of Allah?",
    options: [
      "Suratu Ibraheem",
      "Suratun Nuh",
      "Suratul Anbiyaa",
      "Suratul A’la",
      "Suratul Mudathir",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Which is the longest chapter of the Quran?",
    options: [
      "Suratul A’raf",
      "Suratul Baqarah",
      "Suratul An’am",
      "Suratul Maidah",
      "Suratul Nisaa",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which chapter of the Quran falls between Suratul Duha and Suratul Tin?",
    options: [
      "Suratul Layl",
      "Suratul ‘Alaq",
      "Suratus-Sharh",
      "Suratul Qadr",
      "Suratul Bayyinah",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which Chapter of the Quran starts with the name of two fruits?",
    options: [
      "Suratul Tin",
      "Suratul Najm",
      "Suratul Falaq",
      "Suratul ‘Adiyaat",
      "Suratul Humazah",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Who are the Qurahu Sab’u (the Seven Reciters) of the Quran?",
    options: [
      "Al Hassan al Basriy, Ibn Kathir Al Makiy, Abu ‘Amru bn ‘Ulahi, Ibn ‘Aamir Damashqiy, ‘Asimu bn Abi Najudi Al Kufiy, Hamza bn Habeeb Azzayyat and Al Kisaiyy",
      "Nafi’u Madaniy, Ibn Kathir Al Makiy, Abu ‘Amru bn ‘Ulahi, Ibn ‘Aamir Damashqiy, ‘Asimu bn Abi Najudi Al Kufiy, Khalaf bn Hisham al Bazzar and Al Kisaiyy",
      "Nafi’u Madaniy, Ibn Kathir Al Makiy, Ya’qub Hadramiy, Ibn ‘Aamir Damashqiy, ‘Asimu bn Abi Najudi Al Kufiy, Hamza bn Habee Azzayyat and Al Kisaiyy",
      "Nafi’u Madaniy, Ibn Kathir Al Makiy, Abu ‘Amru bn ‘Ulahi, Ibn ‘Aamir Damashqiy, ‘Asimu bn Abi Najudi Al Kufiy, Hamza bn Habeeb Azzayyat and Al Kisaiyy",
      "Nafi’u Madaniy, Ibn Kathir Al Makiy, Abu Ja’far Yazid bn Qa’qaa’, Ibn ‘Aamir Damashqiy, ‘Asimu bn Abi Najudi Al Kufiy, Hamza bn Habee Azzayyat and Al Kisaiyy",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "How many Juzh (part) are in the Quran?",
    options: ["6666", "313", "114", "60", "30"],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which 10 verses of the Quran can protect us from afflictions of Masih Dajjal, if we memorise them?",
    options: [
      "last 10 verses of Suratul Baqarah",
      "First 10 verses of Suratu Yasin",
      "First 10 verses of Suratul Kahf",
      "First 10 verses of Suratul Qamar",
      "First 10 verses of Suratul Rahman",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the greatest Ayat (verse) of the Quran?",
    options: [
      "Ayatul Dayn",
      "Ayatul Kursiy",
      "Yasin",
      "Ayatul Qital",
      "Alif Lam Mim",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "“This day, I have perfected your religion for you, completed My favour upon you, and I have chosen for you Islam as your religion…” Q5:3. This was revealed to Prophet Muhammad (May the peace and blessing of Allaah be upon him) while he's  on the mount of Arafat. Does this verse a part of what is Called Meccan verse or Medinan verse?",
    options: [
      "Meccan verse",
      "Medinan verse",
      "‘Arafah verse",
      "Fatih verse",
      "Hudaibiyah verse",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which Chapter of the Quran mentioned in it the name of Prophet Yusuph (May the peace be upon him) apart from Suratu Yusuph and Suratul An’am?",
    options: [
      "Suratul Baqarah",
      "Suratul Qasas",
      "Suratus Saffat",
      "Suratul Gafir",
      "Suratul Israil",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Which Chapter is the shortest Chapter of the Quran?",
    options: [
      "Suratul Ikhlas",
      "Suratul Nasr",
      "Suratul Quraish",
      "Suratul ‘Asr",
      "Suratul Kawthar",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How many Chapter’s name of the Quran have the names of Messengers of Allaah?",
    options: ["6", "5", "4", "3", "2"],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "How many Chapters of the Quran start with Ha Meem?",
    options: ["6", "7", "8", "9", "10"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which month was the Quran revealed?",
    options: ["Muharram", "Rajab", "Sha’ban", "Ramadan", "Dhul Hijjah"],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Which Chapter of the Quran mentioned Milk in it?",
    options: [
      "Suratul Hujrat",
      "Suratu Muhammad",
      "Suratun Najm",
      "Suratul Maryam",
      "Suratul Waqi’ah",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
];
export default dayTwentySixQuestions;
